Guide to the Public Art Fund Archive 1966-2009 MSS.270
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VIII: Susan Freedman Papers, 192111
  - Panel Chair, MTA Artist Selection, 1986; 196776 (Box 77, Folder 20)
  - Catalina Parra, 1986; 196777 (Box 77, Folder 21)
  - Lecture, Citizens Union of NYC, September 25, 1986; 196778 (Box 77, Folder 22)
  - The Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1987; 196779 (Box 77, Folder 23)
  - Westchester Public Art, 1985; 196780 (Box 77, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, 1986-1989; 196781 (Box 77, Folder 25)
  - Annual Report Letters of Congratulations, undated; 196782 (Box 77, Folder 26)
  - Susan's Betsy file - current, undated; 196789 (Box 77, Folder 27)
  - Press - Susan Freedman - New President of Public Art Fund, 1985-1986; 196794 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - The President's Council - Urban Center, 1986-1987; 196805 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - William H. Whyte's Chapter 9 - Public Art Book Chapter, 1987-1988; 196747 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Charter Member, City Parks Foundation, 1989; 196807 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Athena Foundation, Socrates Sculpture Park, 1987-1990; 196809 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Arts and Business Council, 1986-1989; 196810 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Biography, 1986-1988; 196811 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - City Parks Foundation, 1991-1993; 196812 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Fine Arts Federation, 1986-1991; 196813 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Susan Freedman Correspondence, 1981-1992; 196814 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Municipal Art Society, undated; 196815 (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - Municipal Art - Kid City Program, undated; 196816 (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - List Art Center / Fine Arts Federation of Art, undated; 196817 (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - NYC Historic Properties Fund, 1991; 196818 (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - Panel, undated; 196819 (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - Press, undated; 196820 (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Stroll, 1987; 196821 (Box 78, Folder 17)
  - Art Table, Inc., 1987-1990; 196808 (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - Jim Clark File, 1995; 196822 (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - West Side Task Force, 1987; 201876 (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Benefit Report book, 1991; 201877 (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - Benefit Dinner, 1993; 201878 (Box 121, Folder 5)
  - Lower Manhattan Guide, 1996; 201879 (Box 121, Folder 6)
  - Alamo - Tony Rosenthal, undated; 201880 (Box 121, Folder 7)
  - Photographs, undated; 201881 (Box 121, Folder 8)
- Series IX: Photographic Material, 179239
  The photographs in this series do not include photos from all Public Art Fund projects. The bulk of the project photographs are found within each project folder in series I, II, III, and V.
  - Subseries IX.A: City Walls Slides, 1967-1977; 196885
    This series includes slides and negatives from multiple artist projects commissioned by City Walls. The images document the installation and inception of each project.
    - City Walls Slides #1: 1967-1973, 196905 (Box 79)
    - City Walls Slides #2: 1973-1976, 196906 (Box 80)
    - City Walls Slides #3: 1976-1977, 196907 (Box 81)
    - "Environmental Communications" and "Research" Slides, 1972-1976; 197355 (Box 82)
  - Subseries IX.B: Public Art Fund Project Slides, 196921
    Images in this series document various aspects of each exhibition, including photographs of installation, opening receptions, and the work itself.
    - Di Suvero, Mark - 1 of 4, [1993]; 196927 (Box 83)
    - Di Suvero, Mark - 2 of 4, [1993]; 196928 (Box 84)
    - Di Suvero, Mark - 3 of 4, [1993]; 196929 (Box 85)
    - Di Suvero, Mark - 4 of 4, [1993]; 198148 (Box 86)
    - Smith, Tony, 1998; 200757 (Box 88)
    - Kabakov, Ilya - "Palace of Projects", 2000; 197559 (Box 87)
    - Paine, Roxy - "Bluff", 2002; 197560 (Box 88)
    - Murakami, Takeshi - Opening Photos, 2003; 196926 (Box 89)
    - Governor's Island opening images, 2004; 200766 (Box 90)
    - Unidentified project images - opening - Isabella Rossellini, undated; 200767 (Box 90)
    - Smith, Allison - "The Muster"/ Photographs by Aaron Diskin - 1 of 4, 2005; 196919 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Smith, Allison - "The Muster"/ Photographs by Aaron Diskin - 2 of 4, 2005; 196920 (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Smith, Allison - "The Muster"/ Photographs by Aaron Diskin - 3 of 4, 2005; 200768 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Smith, Allison - "The Muster"/ Photographs by Aaron Diskin - 4 of 4, 2005; 200769 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Subseries IX.C: Duplicate slides and project images from Public Art Fund photo Archive, undated; 196924
    This series includes duplicate slides de-accessioned from the Public Art Fund's slide library. Original images from this series are still housed on site at the Public Art Fund.
    - Duplicate slides 1970-1983, 198245 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Katz, Alex - Duplicate Slides "Nine Women", 1977-1987; 198241 (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - Van Dalen, Anton - Duplicate Slides, 1983-1987; 198236 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Duplicate Slides 1996-2003, 198242 (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Haring, Keith - Duplicate Slides, 1997; 198237 (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - Koons, Jeff - Installation Slides - Duplicates, 2000; 198238 (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - Embassy Hotel - Research, undated; 198244 (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - Lecture Slides, undated; 198240 (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - Possible Site Photos for Urban Environment Site Sculpture Project, undated; 198243 (Box 92, Folder 9)
    - Programs - PR Support, undated; 198246 (Box 92, Folder 10)
    - Research Images- Acconci, Vito - bus shelter and others, undated; 198239 (Box 92, Folder 11)
    - Research slides- Smith, Tony; Acconci, Vito, undated; 198235 (Box 92, Folder 12)
- Series X: Video, 179240
  This series contains all video recordings from the Public Art Fund Archive. Items are arranged chronologically by date of creation, and then alphabetically by title. Material includes video documentation of artist projects, recorded news broadcasts, and interviews with artists. This series includes videotaped footage of "Messages to the Public", shot at Times Square over a ten-year period. Descriptions are derived from the original cassette or container annotations and include title, date, the original format of video, and the total running time (TRT).
  - Subseries X.A: Access Copies, 179668
    - Public Art Fund's Messages to the Public, 1982--1990, 198067 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 270.0013, E-records fales_mss270, Case 270.0013)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
      Format: VHS
      TRT: 00:30:00
    - Towards a Livable City - New Deal Films, Inc. - 5/6/82, 1982; 198068 (Case 270.0020)
      TRT: 00:16:45
    - Towards a Livable City - New Deal Films, Inc. - 5/6/82, 1982; 198069 (Case 270.0021)
    - Public Art Fund Inc. - "Messages to the Public" - July 1988 to May 1989, 1988-1989; 198071 (Case 270.0060)
      TRT: 00:10:00
    - Public Art Fund Inc. - "Messages to the Public" - June 1989 to September 1990, 1989-1990; 198073 (Case 270.0068)
      TRT: 00:15:00
    - 30-sec. Television PSA on AIDS By Bing Lee and Garson Yu, 1992; 198078 (Case 270.0096)
      TRT: 00:00:30
    - 30 Sec. Spot on AIDS - Multi Reel (5 Languages) - Bing Lee/Garson Yu, 1992; 198079 (Case 270.0097)
    - Paine Webber Art Gallery, 1994; 198080 (Case 270.0107)
      TRT: 00:05:00
    - Ruder Finn - Children Speak PSA, 1995; 198082 (Case 270.0116)
      TRT: 00:01:22
    - New York Views - WABC-TV (ABC) New York [Kruger], 1997; 198083 (Case 270.0132)
      TRT: 00:04:49
    - Public Art Fund June 1998, 198088 (Case 270.0138)
    - Public Art Fund June 1998, 198089 (Case 270.0139)
    - Sample Videos, Jocelyn Taylor, 2000; 198090 (Case 270.0170)
    - Sunday Morning - Andy Goldsworthy, 2003; 198091 (Case 270.0227)
    - Doris Freedman Award, 2005; 198092 (Case 270.0254)
    - Art at Hilton Time Square, undated; 198093 (Case 270.0270)
      TRT: 00:11:00
  - Subseries X.B: Originals, 197027
    - WCBS - TV - "Living Sculpture in Soho", May 22, 1978; 197576 (Box 93, Media ID: 270.0001)
      Format: 3/4" Umatic
      TRT: 00:00:20
    - "Messages to the Public" - New Year's Eve Show / 1981-982 Times Square Spectacolor Display, 1981-1982; 197578 (Box 93, Media ID: 270.0003)
    - "Messages to the Public" - New Year's Eve Show / 1981-1982 Times Square Spectacolor Display, 197577 (Box 93, Media ID: 270.0002)
    - "Messages to the Public" - New Year's Eve Show, 1982; 197579 (Box 93, Media ID: 270.0004)
    - SPECTRACOLOR NEW YEARS PUBLIC ART FUND (DUB), 1982; 197580 (Box 93, Media ID: 270.0005)
    - 1982 New Years, 197581 (Box 93, Media ID: 270.0006)
    - [Sheta 3, Aricle Beucler, Killi Melawid], 1982; 197583 (Box 93, Media ID: 270.0007)
    - McN - LEHR/ Profile: Jenny Holzer: Benches - '89, MTTP - '82, Sign on Truck -'84, 1982; 197582 (Box 93, Media ID: 270.0008)
    - Public Art Fund Inc. - Compilation Tape sent to NYSCA - Messages to the Public, 1982; 197590 (Box 93, Media ID: 270.0009)
    - PUBLIC ART FUND SPECTRACOLOR BOARD / "MESSAGES TO THE PUBLIC", 1982; 197593 (Box 93, Media ID: 270.0010)
    - PUBLIC ART FUND's Messages to the Public, 1982-1990 A nine year program on the Spectacolor lightboard, Times Square, NYC., 197594 (Box 93, Media ID: 270.0011)
      TRT: 00.30.00
    - PUBLIC ART FUND's Messages to the Public, 1982-1990 A nine year program on the Spectacolor lightboard, Times Square, NYC. - ALL, 197595 (Box 93, Media ID: 270.0012)
    - PUBLIC ART FUND 82-83 / "MESSAGES TO THE PUBLIC", 1982-1983; 197602 (Box 93, Media ID: 270.0014)
    - "Towards A Livable City", 1982; 197612 (Box 93, Media ID: 270.0015)
      Format: BetacamSP
    - "Towards A Livable City", 1982; 197613 (Box 93, Media ID: 270.0016)
    - "Towards a Livable City", New Deal Films, Inc., 1982; 197614 (Box 93, Media ID: 270.0017)
    - "Towards a Livable City", 1982; 197615 (Box 93, Media 270.0018)
    - "Towards a Livable City", 1982; 197616 (Box 93, Media ID: 270.0019)
    - Spectacolor Computer Animated Lightboard / "Messages to the Public" - Times Square - Gary Falk, November 1983; 197617 (Box 93, Media ID: 270.0022)
    - Interview - Public Art Fund II - Dixon, 1983; 197618 (Box 93, Media ID: 270.0023)
    - SPECTACOLOR PUBLIC ART FUND XI - ORIG 3, 1984; 197619 (Box 93, Media ID: 270.0024)
    - PUBLIC ART FUND SPECTACOLOR ORIG 1 - [M. Gellar], 1984; 197620 (Box 93, Media ID: 270.0025)
      TRT: 00.03:55
    - SPECTACOLOR 2 -Stein to Haring, 1984; 197621 (Box 94, Media ID: 270.0026)
    - SPECTACOLOR COPY -ART FUND XI 84, 1984; 197622 (Box 94, Media ID: 270.0027)
    - PUBLIC ART FUND Video documentation compilation, April 1984; 197623 (Box 94, Media ID: 270.0028)
    - Jenny Holzer - "Sign on a Truck" - Original, 1984; 197624 (Box 94, Media ID: 270.0029)
    - "Sign on a Truck Documentary", 1984; 197625 (Box 94, Media ID: 270.0030)
    - Art Fund 1985 House Copy, 197626 (Box 94, Media ID: 270.0031)
    - Judith Barry - "Messages to the Public" - December 1985 - Censored, 197627 (Box 94, Media ID: 270.0032)
    - SPECTACOLOR 1, 1985; 197628 (Box 94, Media ID: 270.0033)
    - Public Art Fund - "Messages to the Public" - 1985, 197629 (Box 94, Media ID: 270.0034)
    - "29 Food Nude in Bryant Park {Myrrha/ P.I.A.}", January 1985; 197630 (Box 94, Media ID: 270.0035)
    - "Chain Reaction" (Sample Reel) - Lynn Hershman, 1985; 197631 (Box 94, Media ID: 270.0036)
    - "MTTP" - 1986, 197632 (Box 94, Media ID: 270.0037)
    - Public Art Fund - "Messages to the Public" - Spectraboard - Titled - Submaster for copies, 1986; 197633 (Box 94, Media ID: 270.0038)
    - Messages to the Public - FY86-87 Final Report, 1986; 197634 (Box 94, Media ID: 270.0039)
    - SPECTACOLOR '86 - Camera original, 1986; 197635 (Box 94, Media ID: 270.0040)
    - SPECTACOLOR - "Messages to the Public" - Edited - Copy, 1986; 197636 (Box 94, Media ID: 270.0041)
    - SPECTACOLOR - 86 - Edited Copy, 1986; 197637 (Box 94, Media ID: 270.0042)
    - Dupe of "MTTP 1996", 1986; 197638 (Box 94, Media ID: 270.0043)
    - Media Mass by Les Levine, 1986; 197639 (Box 94, Media ID: 270.0044)
    - Public Art Fund - Master, 1987; 197640 (Box 94, Media ID: 270.0045)
    - Public Art Fund - Excerpt Short - Master, 1987; 197641 (Box 94, Media ID: 270.0046)
    - Public Art Fund - Spectacolor - Original 3, 1987; 197642 (Box 95, Media ID: 270.0047)
    - Public Art Fund - Spectacolor - Original 2, 1987; 197643 (Box 95, Media ID: 270.0048)
    - Public Art Fund - Times Square Day + Nite, 1987; 197644 (Box 95, Media ID: 270.0049)
    - Judith Barry, 1988; 197645 (Box 95, Media ID: 270.0050)
    - "Messages to the Public" - Public Art Fund - Dub, 1988-1989; 197646 (Box 95, Media ID: 270.0051)
    - P.A.F. - Master, 1988; 197647 (Box 95, Media ID: 270.0052)
    - Public Art Fund - Spectacolor - [Cam. Orig. 1], 1988; 197648 (Box 95, Media ID: 270.0053)
    - "Messages to the Public", 1988-1989; 197649 (Box 95, Media ID: 270.0054)
    - "Messages to the Public", 1988-1989; 197650 (Box 95, Media ID: 270.0055)
    - "Messages to the Public", 1988-1989; 197651 (Box 95, Media ID: 270.0056)
    - "Messages to the Public", 1988-1989; 197652 (Box 95, Media ID: 270.0057)
    - "Messages to the Public" - Master Tape, 1988-1989; 197653 (Box 95, Media ID: 270.0058)
    - Public Art Fund Inc. - "Messages to the Public", 1988-1989; 197654 (Box 95, Media ID: 270.0059)
    - SPECTACOLOR / Downey-Piper, 1988-1989; 197655 (Box 95, Media ID: 270.0061)
    - SPECTACOLOR BILLBOARD MARCH 1988 - Myrel Chernick, 197656 (Box 95, Media ID: 270.0062)
    - Times Square Sony TV Media Exposure, 1988; 197657 (Box 95, Media ID: 270.0063)
    - Willie Birth, "For Old Bone and Southern Memorie." - Reception Fort Greene, 1988; 197658 (Box 95, Media ID: 270.0064)
    - Public Art Fund - "Messages to the Public", 1989-1990; 197659 (Box 95, Media ID: 270.0065)
    - Public Art Fund - "Messages to the Public", 1989-1990; 197660 (Box 95, Media ID: 270.0066)
      TRT: 00:10:41
    - "Messages to the Public", 1989-1990; 197661 (Box 95, Media ID: 270.0067)
    - "Messages to the Public", 1989-1990; 197662 (Box 95, Media ID: 270.0069)
    - "Messages to the Public", 1989-1990; 197663 (Box 95, Media ID: 270.0070)
    - "Messages to the Public" Spectacolor Lightboard - One Times Square, 1989; 197664 (Box 95, Media ID: 270.0071)
    - TIMESQUARE SHOOT, 1989; 197665 (Box 96, Media ID: 270.0072)
    - SPECTACOLOR - PAF #1 - Standard - Original, 1989; 197666 (Box 96, Media ID: 270.0073)
    - SPECTRACOLOR - #2 - Zooms & Cutaways - Original, 1989; 197667 (Box 96, Media ID: 270.0074)
    - SPECTACOLOR - PAF - "Messages to the Public", 1989; 197668 (Box 96, Media ID: 270.0075)
    - [Speta 4 + 2nd part 2 + All Part 3], 1989; 197669 (Box 96, Media ID: 270.0076)
      TRT: [00:11:43]
    - [Haring - Good PAF Wide], 1989; 197670 (Box 96, Media ID: 270.0077)
    - Public Art Fund / "Messages to the Public", June 1989 - September 1990; 197671 (Box 96, Media ID: 270.0078)
    - Today Show - B. Goldner, 1990; 197672 (Box 96, Media ID: 270.0079)
    - Michel Goulet - Raw Footage Tape 1 of 5 - Master, 1990; 197673 (Box 96, Media ID: 270.0080)
    - Michel Goulet - Raw Footage Tape 2 of 5 - Master, 1990; 197674 (Box 96, Media ID: 270.0081)
    - Michel Goulet - Raw Footage Tape 3 of 5 - Master, 1990; 197675 (Box 96, Media ID: 270.0082)
    - Michel Goulet - Raw Footage Tape 4 of 5 - Master, 1990; 197676 (Box 96, Media ID: 270.0083)
    - Michel Goulet - Raw Footage Tape 5 of 5 - Master, 1990; 197677 (Box 96, Media ID: 270.0084)
    - Michel Goulet - Raw Footage Tape 1 of 1 - Copy, 1990; 197678 (Box 96, Media ID: 270.0085)
    - Michel Goulet - Les Lieux Communs (Raw Footage) - Copy, 1990; 197679 (Box 96, Media ID: 270.0086)
    - Compilation Tape of Goulet, Muntadas, Holzer, 1991; 197680 (Box 96, Media ID: 270.0087)
    - [Tomi Serra - Muntadas's "The Limousine Project"] - Dub, 1991; 197681 (Box 96, Media ID: 270.0088)
    - Public Art Fund: "Newsstands", 1992; 197682 (Box 96, Media ID: 270.0089)
    - AIDS VIDEO PROJECT (English Version), [1992]; 197683 (Box 96, Media ID: 270.0090)
    - 30 Second PSA on Aids by Bing Lee and Garson Yu, [1992]; 197684 (Box 96, Media ID: 270.0091)
    - 30 Second Spot on AIDS, [1992]; 197685 (Box 96, Media ID: 270.0092)
    - 30 Second Spot on AIDS, [1992]; 197686 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0093)
    - 30 Second Spot on AIDS by Bing Lee and Garson Yu, 1992; 197687 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0094)
    - 30 Second Spot on AIDS, [1992]; 197688 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0095)
    - "Diverse Roots, Diverse Forms" (English), 1993; 197689 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0098)
      TRT: 00:27:45
    - Rhonda Roland Shearer - US Women's Awareness, 1993; 197690 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0099)
    - Botero (Catalogue) - Champs Elysees - Paris, 1993; 197691 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0100)
    - "Botero in N.Y." - CNN International, 1993; 197692 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0101)
    - "Botero in N.Y." - CBS Sunday Morning, 1993; 197693 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0102)
    - PAF - "Botero in N.Y." - "New York Views" - [WABC-TV], 1993; 197694 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0103)
    - PAF - "Botero in N.Y." - "5:00 News" - WCBS-TV, 1993; 197695 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0104)
    - PAF - "Botero in N.Y." - CNN - "Showbiz Today", 1993; 197696 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0105)
    - Paine Webber Art Gallery - Views WABC TV, 1994; 197697 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0106)
    - Partnerships for Community - Phipps House, 1994; 197698 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0108)
    - City Arts Show #206, 1995; 197699 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0109)
    - Ruder Finn - Children Speak PSA, 1995; 197706 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0110)
    - Tom Otterness - "Newsreel" - Ch7, 1995-1996; 197700 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0111)
    - Tom Otterness - "Local Focus" - CH4, 1996; 197701 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0112)
    - City Arts: Canvassing NY, Pascal Giraudon + Chris Doyle, 1996; 197703 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0113)
    - Public Art Fund - "City Arts" - Christo, 1996; 197704 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0114)
    - Carmen / Susan K. Freedman, 1996; 197705 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0115)
    - "Gondolas in Subway Station" - Chicago & Cable Coverage, 1996; 197707 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0117)
    - Chris Doyle/Gold Bridge, 1996; 197702 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0118)
    - "Chris Doyle/Gold Bridge", 1996; 197708 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0119)
    - "Neighborhoods" - Channel 4 - Alexander Brodsky #9, 1996; 197709 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0120)
    - Alexander Brodsky - "A Different Story" - CNN, 1996-1997; 197710 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0121)
    - Daniel Pflumm - CNN Loops, 1997; 197711 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0122)
      TRT: 00:32:00
    - MetroTech Art, 1997; 197712 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0123)
    - LaDolce Vito #206 - Alison Saar + Vito Acconci, 1997; 197713 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0124)
    - Keith Haring on Park Avenue, 1997; 197714 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0125)
    - New York Close-Up, 1997; 197715 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0126)
    - "Keith Haring Exhibit/Public Art Fund", 1997; 197716 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0127)
    - "Keith Haring/Whitney Museum", 1997; 197717 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0128)
      TRT: 00:06:00
    - "Keith Haring Exhibit", 1997; 197718 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0129)
      TRT: 1:36
    - New York Views - WABC-TV, 1997; 197719 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0130)
    - New York Views - WABC-TV (Kruger), 1997; 197720 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0131)
    - The Wall, 1997; 197721 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0133)
    - "Donald Lipsky/Sculpture", 1998; 197722 (Box 98, Media ID: 270.0134)
      TRT: 00:01:52
    - The Public Art Fund Montage, 1998; 197724 (Box 98, Media ID: 270.0135)
    - The Public Art Fund Montage, 1998; 197725 (Box 98, Media ID: 270.0136)
    - The Public Art Fund Montage, 1998; 197726 (Box 98, Media ID: 270.0137)
    - "Rodin Exhibit", 1998; 197727 (Box 98, Media ID: 270.0140)
    - "Iris Cantor/Rodin Sculpture", 1998; 197728 (Box 98, Media ID: 270.0141)
      TRT: 00:02:00
    - "Iris Cantor", 1998; 197729 (Box 98, Media ID: 270.0142)
      TRT: 00:01:51
    - "Public Art Fund/Giant Sculptures", 1998; 197730 (Box 98, Media ID: 270.0143)
      TRT: 00:00:17
    - "Henry Street Art/Public Art Fund", 1998; 197731 (Box 98, Media ID: 270.0144)
      TRT: 00:02:46
    - "Raugh" - Andrea Zittel, 1998; 197732 (Box 98, Media ID: 270.0145)
    - Kirsten Mosher - "Ballpark Traffic", 1998; 197733 (Box 98, Media ID: 270.0146)
    - "Water Tower Movie", Rachel Whiteread, 1998; 197734 (Box 98, Media ID: 270.0147)
    - The Public Art Fund - Sara Booth - Bloomberg, 1998; 197735 (Box 98, Media ID: 270.0148)
    - CBS Sunday Morning "Cowtown USA", 1999; 197736 (Box 98, Media ID: 270.0149)
    - EGG The Arts Show #101 - Art. Who Needs It? - Kristen Jones, Andrew Ginzel, 1999; 197737 (Box 98, Media ID: 270.0150)
      TRT: 00:26:46
    - New Urban Sculpture: MetroTech Center, 1999; 197738 (Box 98, Media ID: 270.0151)
    - "Orpheus Descending (As the World Turns)", 1999; 197739 (Box 98, Media ID: 270.0152)
    - Daniel Pflumm - "In Hope for the Best", 1999; 197740 (Box 98, Media ID: 270.0153)
      TRT: 00:20:00
    - "Susan Freedman/Paine Webber Art Gallery", 1999; 197741 (Box 98, Media ID: 270.0154)
      TRT: 00:01:40
    - "Red Hook", 1999; 197742 (Box 98, Media ID: 270.0155)
      TRT: 00:04:00
    - "Public Art Fund" - Hourly News - New York One TV Cable, 1999; 197745 (Box 98, Media ID: 270.0156)
      TRT: 00:03:05
    - RSI - CRESMAC - MACA / Prep, 1999; 197753 (Box 98, Media ID: 270.0157)
    - "Public Art Fund" - Hourly News - New York One, October 30, 1999; 197754 (Box 98, Media ID: 270.0158)
      TRT: 00:03:03
    - "Public Art Fund/ Susan Freedman" - News All Day - New York One, November 30, 1999; 197755 (Box 98, Media ID: 270.0159)
      TRT: 00:03:43
    - "Tom Eccles/Public Art Fund" - Weekend Metroguide Cable, December 30, 1999; 197762 (Box 98, Media ID: 270.0160)
      TRT: 00:07:22
    - "Open My Glade" - Pipilotti Rist, 2000; 197764 (Box 98, Media ID: 270.0161)
    - Shimon Attie - "An Unusually Bad Lot, 2000; 197765 (Box 98, Media ID: 270.0162)
    - Bloomberg Television - Public Art Fund - Andrea Zittel, 2000; 197767 (Box 98, Media ID: 270.0163)
    - Beecroft Briefing Tape, 2000; 197768 (Box 98, Media ID: 270.0164)
    - VB42 - The Silent Service In Cooperation with the Undersea Warfare Community - Vanessa Beecroft, 2000; 197769 (Box 98, Media ID: 270.0165)
      TRT: 00:25:18
    - First Person, Third Party - Anissa Mack, 2000; 197770 (Box 98, Media ID: 270.0166)
    - Target Marketing Video, 2000; 197771 (Box 98, Media ID: 270.0167)
      TRT: 00:07:09
    - Test in Madison Square Park - Tony Oursler, 2000; 197772 (Box 98, Media ID: 270.0168)
    - Sample Videos - Jocelyn Taylor, 2000; 197773 (Box 98, Media ID: 270.0169)
    - The Story of Color - Jocelyn Taylor, 2000; 197776 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0171)
    - Main Video I: Foundation, Erection, Scaffolding for "Puppy," Jeff Koons, 2000; 197777 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0172)
    - Party, Fabric + Soil, Flower-Planting, De-Install for Puppy, Jeff Koons, 2000; 197778 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0173)
    - Paul Pfeiffer - Sample footage - "Orpheus Descending, 2000; 197779 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0174)
      TRT: 3 min.
    - "Orpheus Descending", 2000; 197780 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0175)
    - "Time Square Art Exhibition", 2000; 197781 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0176)
      TRT: 00:03:00
    - "Public Art Fund Tom Eccles", 2000; 197782 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0177)
      TRT: 00:02:50
    - Art at Hilton Times Square/Embassy Suites, Daniel Aubry, 2000; 197783 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0178)
    - "Public Art Fund/Jeff Koons/Dog Sculpture", 2000; 197784 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0179)
    - Madison Park Test - Tony Oursler, 2000; 197785 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0180)
    - "Orpheus Descending" 11AM Test Tape - Paul Pfeiffer, 2000; 197786 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0181)
    - Public Art Fund, 2000; 197787 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0182)
    - Public Art Fund: Susan Freedman at Bloomberg, 2000; 197788 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0183)
    - "Target Art in the Park", 2000; 197789 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0184)
    - "Tom Eccles-Manhole Covers", 2000; 197790 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0185)
      TRT: 00:02:14
    - "Rockefeller Plaza Spider Exhibit", 2001; 197791 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0186)